consumersrvycnter.com 2017-06-06

# 

**RewardZoneUSA, LLC  Privacy Policy**

**Policy Last Revised: April 13, 2016**

The following outlines our policy (Policy) for collecting and using information that is personally identifiable to a user  (PII) and information that is not personally identifiable to a user (non-PII) by RewardZone USA LLC (RewardZone, we, or us) from our websites, and other websites we own and operate that promote incentives (collectively, Websites).   For purposes of this Policy, PII and non-PII will be referred to as Information.  

By accessing and using a Website, you agree to the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree to and accept these terms, please do not use or visit a Website or participate in any promotion offered or promoted on a Website. We also describe additional rights that California users have under the California “Shine the Light” law.   

**HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED**

Here are some of the ways we collect Information from users:

·       Registration forms and surveys;

·       By tracking users’ online behavior on our Websites;

·       Emails, telephone calls, USPS mail and other customer service or other contacts with users;

·       Through the use of “cookies” (small text files placed on a user’s computer that track online behavior), single-pixel GIF image files (also called “web beacons”) and other technological means; and

·       Information provided to claim an incentive.

We permit third parties to advertise and promote our Websites and we may place and permit third parties to place advertising, cookies, web beacons and other content, including links to other websites on our Websites. We and our third party marketing partners may use these technological means placed on our Websites to collect and share Information. We are not responsible for the Information they collect or for their use of this Information or for the privacy practices of other websites that are linked to our Websites.

**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Here are some of the types of Information we collect from users:

• Name                                   • Postal address                                 • E-mail address

• Telephone number           • Cell/landline phone number         • Gender and date of birth

• IP Address                           • Survey responses                            • Device ID & location

• Browser User Agent • Referring URL

We may use third party sources to augment and/or verify the Information we collect from users and may also associate demographic and other data we collect such as the user’s browser and device with their Information.

**Children and Non- US Residents** : We don’t knowingly collect or retain information from the Websites from children under the age of 13. The Websites are intended for use by U.S. residents who are not minors. If you are a minor, not a U.S. resident or don’t agree with this Policy’s terms, please don’t access or use our Websites.

**USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION**

We may use Information and share it with third parties (who may compensate us) in many ways and for many purposes including the following:

•       To fulfill an incentive;

•       To maintain suppression or opt-out lists that we may share with third parties so that a user is not contacted when the user has asked not to be;

•       For site operation;

•       To provide users with information and/or offers for products or services from us or third parties;

•       To notify the IRS that a user has received an incentive if the value exceeds the reporting threshold;  

•       To track online behavior for behavioral advertising and other marketing purposes. If a user registers on one of our Websites, the user may receive relevant third party daily emails from that Website, its exclusive emailing partner and other websites we or our affiliates own and operate;

• To develop and/or enhance our Affiliates’ and/or third parties’ products and/or services; 

•       If we are acquired by or merged with another company, we may transfer our users’ information to the acquirer;

•       To respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or when we determine it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or regulations; and

•       To assist with site operation and other communication services, we may share Information with third parties, including vendors and contractors who provide services to us.  

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit use of the Information by these third parties as necessary for the purposes set forth above.  

**Behavioral Advertising:** Behavioral advertising enables us and our third party marketing partners to deliver to users what is hoped to be more relevant information and/or offers for products or services. We and our third party marketing partners may use cookies, web beacons and other technological means to track user’s online behavior and to collect Information that enables the tailoring of targeted offers and advertisements. We may share this and other Information with our third party marketing partners, who may compensate us. We are not responsible for the Information they collect, for their use of this Information or for the privacy practices of other websites that are linked to our Websites.

**Personal Health Information** : Our surveys may ask health-related questions which we may share with our third party marketing partners who advertise health-related products and services on our Websites or who otherwise promote health-related products or services. We will use this health information only with your consent and for the purpose of displaying offers for health-related for products and services or to provide Information to these providers so they can contact you. You may always request modification or removal of your information by contacting us at privacy@rewardzoneusa.com.

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of your Information. We currently do not encrypt Information that we store.  Given the nature of the Internet, your Information passes through entities that we are unable to control.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee that our security measures or those of third parties who access or transmit your Information will prevent your Information from being illegally accessed, stolen or altered.

**OPTING-OUT**

Users may opt-out from receiving future offers from us or from our third party marketing partners by following the Opt-Out instructions contained in the marketing communication or by [clicking here](http://contact.rewardzoneusa.com/unsub.aspx).  You may also opt-out from future communications from a third party by contacting them directly.  A third party’s use of Information is subject to their privacy policy and we have no control or responsibility over their use.

Users may opt out from the collection of online viewing data for behavioral advertising purposes by companies who have elected to participate in one of the behavioral advertising opt-out mechanisms such as the Digital Adverting Alliance’s opt-out program located at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). As is the case with most websites, we have not elected to participate in any of these programs at this time or alter our behavior when a user to one of our Websites has activated the “do-not-track” setting on their browser (see, “Browser “Do Not Track” Signals”, described below).

**ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

All users who provide their Information to us may modify and correct their Information by contacting us [here](http://contact.rewardzoneusa.com/contact.aspx). 

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

The California “Shine the Light” law permits users who are California residents to request information regarding our disclosure of their Information to third parties including the categories of Information shared and a list of the names and addresses of third parties with whom the Information was shared.  If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a request by contacting us [here](http://contact.rewardzoneusa.com/contact.aspx).  In your request, please specify that you want "Your RewardzoneUSA LLC California Privacy Rights Notice."  Please allow 30 days for a response. 

**Browser “Do Not Track” Signals:   **Most browsers contain a “do-not-track” setting.  In general, when a “do-not-track” setting is active, the user’s browser notifies other websites that the user does not want their personal information and online behavior to be tracked and used, for example, for behavioral advertising.  As required by recent Shine the Light law amendments we are required to inform you that, as is the case with most websites, we do not honor or alter our behavior when a user to one of our Websites has activated the “do-not-track” setting on his/her browser.

**Changes to this privacy policy:** We reserve the right to revise and update this Policy at any time. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will post notice on our Website. Any such revisions will be effective 30 days after posting to the Website, and will apply to all Information collected by us both before and following the effective date. Your use of a Website or entrance into any sweepstakes or other promotion following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions. Users should periodically visit this page to review our current policies on our collection and use of Information. 

**Questions, Suggestions or to Contact Us:**   If you have any questions, comments, complaints, or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy or our website, please contact us [here](http://contact.rewardzoneusa.com/contact.aspx).

Policy Last Revised: April 13, 2016
